hey guys this looks like a fun one it
wants us to solve for x it says XX - 4 +
1 = 4X -4 if you want to try on your own
pause it right now because I'm going to
solve it in 3 2 1 so for the first step
we want to say x cannot equal 4 and the
reason for that is if x were equal to
four these would be zero in the
denominator and division by Zer is
undefined next I don't really like
fractions so let's get rid of these
denominators and we can do that by
multiplying both sides of the equation
by x - 4 on the left hand side this x -
4 will distribute to both of these terms
it'll distribute to the first term and
it'll distribute to the second term and
on the right hand side it's just going
to be 4 * the x - 4 so now we can
simplify some things for this first
fraction or rational expression we can
divide away the x - 4 from top and
bottom and then for this part anything
times 1 the times 1 isn't doing anything
and then on the right hand side this x -
4 can be divided from top and bottom so
we now have x + x - 4 = 4 we can add 4
both sides on the left hand side we'll
be left with x + x which is 2X and then
on the right hand side 4 + 4 is equal to
8 we can divide both sides by two and
that'll give us X is equal to 4 well the
problem is earlier we said X cannot
equal 4 so since X can't equal four this
is not a valid solution how exciting